<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>www.pomo.tv</title>
  <subtitle>Feed used to post to Twitter @pomo_tv</subtitle>
  <id>http://www.pomo.tv/</id>
  <link href="http://www.pomo.tv/"/>
  <link href="http://www.pomo.tv/twitterfeed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>www.pomo.tv</name>
  </author>
 
    <entry>
    <title>Universal Links, with a Nod to Other Web-Like Advances</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/151531189"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/151531189</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Universal Links, with a Nod to Other Web-Like Advances - @corvino
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Ignore That Young Man From 2014</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/154146675"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/154146675</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Ignore That Young Man From 2014 - @irons
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Fix issue</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/154148473"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/154148473</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Fix issue - @timothyekl
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Runtime Hacking for Fun and Profit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/151482623"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/151482623</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Runtime Hacking for Fun and Profit - @curtclifton
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Competing with Art</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/153679708"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/153679708</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Competing with Art - @apike
Allen spoke about the similarities between indie programmers and artists&#x2F;musicians. Thanks to advances our tools and the community it&#x27;s never been an easier time to get into programming, but that leads to a highly competitive hit-driven economy very similar to music, where it can be hard to get noticed. Sometimes we need to focus on our side projects not for the potential economic gains, but the creative outlet they provide.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Thank You for Bugging me</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/153709408"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/153709408</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Thank You for Bugging me - @_Barajas
Chris provides support for users of Rogue Amoeba’s fine audio software. There is no good substitute for human-to-human support, although technology can provide shortcuts. Chris talked about how technology and humanity intersect in the role of support, and how good support finds the strengths of each to keep a company and its customers happy.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Protocol-Oriented DataSources</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/152193160"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/152193160</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Protocol-Oriented DataSources - @nvh
Niels van Hoorn talks about protocol-oriented datasources. Combining James Bond and Swift, Niels does a live coding deep dive into protocols, extensions and type aliases.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Swift JsonGen, a code generator</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/152054122"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/152054122</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Swift JsonGen, a code generator - @tomlokhorst
Tom Lokhorst talks about parsing JSON in Swift. Why is this such a problem? What libraries are there to solve this problem? And how he created a code generator to deal with JSON once and for all.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Crypto? Been there, done that</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FWHADBbn4Kc"/>
    <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FWHADBbn4Kc</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Crypto? Been there, done that - @krzyzanowskim
Implementing OpenPGP and cryptography on iOS.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Swift C Interoperability</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/142850815"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/142850815</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Swift C Interoperability - @chriseidhof
In this talk, we&#x27;ll look at Swift&#x27;s interoperability with C, and how to wrap C functions in a way that feels native to Swift.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Prototyping anything you can imagine</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/142850816"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/142850816</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Prototyping anything you can imagine - @koenbok
The future of design tools, prototyping and Framer.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Making Apps in Stop-Motion</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/95951952"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/95951952</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Making Apps in Stop-Motion - @giovatardu
We are in the special effects business without even realizing it.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>NSURLProtocol, Foundation&#x27;s man-in-the-middle</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/95956326"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/95956326</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
NSURLProtocol, Foundation&#x27;s man-in-the-middle - @mttrb
Mattt Thompson described NSURLProtocol as &quot;an Apple-sanctioned man-in-the-middle attack.&quot;  Buried deep in Foundation&#x27;s URL Loading System, NSURLProtocol allows us to intercept requests for URLs from the API libraries we are more familiar with, e.g. AFNetworking, NSURLConnection, UIWebView, NSURLDownload.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>KVO Considered Awesome</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/95999854"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/95999854</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
KVO Considered Awesome - @amyruthworrall
A whirlwind tour through Key Value Coding (KVC), Key Value Observing (KVO), and Cocoa Bindings. Amy will explain what these technologies can do, when to use them, what their limitations are, and some tricks to work around common pitfalls. KVO has had a lot of bad press recently, but when used properly it can help you separate concerns and reduce the number of lines of code required for common operations.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Legal Considerations For Contract Developers</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/96004975"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/96004975</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Legal Considerations For Contract Developers - @DamianOS3
Top legal tips for indie developers working on apps for clients, based on the very expensive mistakes I made in my first 5 years of developing apps for clients.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Red Meat and Gin</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/96057339"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/96057339</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Red Meat and Gin - @siegel
Bare Bones Software are widely recognized as one of the longest-lived indie Mac developers, having been in business since 1993. Their longevity stems from how they handle matters that Rich will cover in the talk: product concept, engineering discipline, customer service and support, ecosystem relations, living with Apple, and dealing with the unpredictable.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sound Debugging</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/96070920"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/96070920</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Sound Debugging - @qnoid
Sound debugging is about elevating Xcode&#x27;s ability to play sounds on a breakpoint to visualise code execution
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tips and tricks for recording your meetup presentations</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/96107143"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/96107143</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Tips and tricks for recording your meetup presentations - @seanwoodhouse
Today there are thousands of iOS and Mac developers meeting up and presenting awesome content all around the world. In this talk Sean will offer some helpful tips on recording, editing and publishing your meetup presentations for everyone to enjoy.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What’s it like to fiddle Mail’s bits?</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/96077948"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/96077948</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
What’s it like to fiddle Mail’s bits? - @littleknown
Let me give you all a quick view from a totally different place than App Stores, nice simple Cocoa code and easily reusable Open Source projects. Writing Mail plugins is a pain in the ass that gives you tremendous challenges every day. I don’t recommend it, but I do enjoy it.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>While Nobody is Looking</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/96086552"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/96086552</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
While Nobody is Looking - @_DavidSmith
There is a natural pull towards focussing on the visual design of an application. Your choice of color, typography and structure all directly impact how your user will experience your app. But what happens when your user isn’t looking? Designing applications for use by increasingly distracted users requires thinking about your customer from a completely different perspective. Building on lessons learned from years of building audio focused applications these are some guides for ensuring your design is usable in ANY context.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Kitchen Sink Database</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/96172262"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/96172262</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
The Kitchen Sink Database - @cparnot
A database is where you store your data. But in practice, your database scheme can quickly grow to become an untamed beast that makes you cry at night. To improve performance, you have the infamous `full_name` column living next to `first_name` and `last_name`; and then there’s `canonical_full_name` for proper search; and `needs_thumbnail` to keep track of thumbnail operations; and an extra table to normalize some relationships needed in the UI; and so on.  Every time you change the UI or add features, your database scheme gets more complicated. Maybe you did survive the software updates, the not-so-automatic migrations, the if statements littered around and the special `rebuildCache` methods. But now your f*^%$@ users want syncing, and you fear for your sanity. Here is the problem: your database is used both for **storing** the actual data and for **displaying** that data and managing the UI. Your data model is torn between two antagonistic goals, and you have a kitchen sink database. I propose a different approach where you explicitly separate those two functions, and with which you can ultimately get your sanity back.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Not Invented Here</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/97058344"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/97058344</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Not Invented Here - @mzarra
We often hear the phrase “Don’t re-invent the wheel.” But what does that really mean? In this session Marcus will be discussing his opinion on this often quoted phrase as well as a discussion of the impacts he is seeing of third party libraries.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Another approach to observation</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/97102055"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/97102055</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Another approach to observation - @tonklon
In this session Tobias  introduces the audience to another possibility to implement the observer pattern in Cocoa, besides KVO and NotificationCenter.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Land or Slam</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/97114266"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/97114266</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
Land or Slam - @lucvandal
How lessons I’ve learned from skateboarding have influenced my current business.
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A Bil-centric view of product development</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://vimeo.com/97201703"/>
    <id>https://vimeo.com/97201703</id>
    <updated>2016-03-07T10:12:47Z</updated>
    <content type="text/plain">
A Bil-centric view of product development - @dlpasco
Essentially, given an extraordinarily gifted developer - take Bil, our CTO -, there are things outside his area of expertise that he&#x27;s recognized as hugely important to making a great app. He wants these people and things because they help him make something even greater: great design, great QA, support, the ability to reach a huge number of users (strong brand, really useful app, great content, etc)
    </content>
  </entry>


</feed>
